<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Dylan Cromer</title>
    <link>//dylancromer.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Dylan Cromer</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2019 19:48:45 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="//dylancromer.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Test-Driven Development for Scientific Programming, Part 2: Getting Started with Python</title>
      <link>//dylancromer.com/programming/tdd2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2019 19:48:45 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//dylancromer.com/programming/tdd2/</guid>
      <description>More Realistic Testing Scenarios&amp;nbsp;¶ In the last part I outlined a brief description of TDD using the example of writing a function in Python that adds numpy arrays together. Of course in actual research, the problem you are trying to solve with code is usually a lot more complicated than just adding a few arrays. Usually you have a more complex calculation consisting of many steps, which might be performed on data in a processing pipeline.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Test-Driven Development for Scientific Programming, Part 1: Introduction</title>
      <link>//dylancromer.com/programming/tdd/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2019 21:59:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//dylancromer.com/programming/tdd/</guid>
      <description>Test-driven development (TDD) is a way of writing code via creating tests, and using the tests to do design on your system. My best summary in a sentence is that TDD exists to focus the difficulty of designing programs into smaller, controllable pieces, in the form of tests.
If you&amp;rsquo;re looking for a more solid definition of TDD, I invite you to watch this video of Gary Bernhardt explaining it very succinctly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>//dylancromer.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//dylancromer.com/about/</guid>
      <description>I am Dylan Cromer. I was a cosmologist with extensive experience studying galaxy cluster masses, using a variety of statistical and computational techniques. After that, I started to focus on a personal research project about structural problems in academia that lead to abuse, poor mental health of grad students, and other problems. My goal is to eventually publish this research. I am currently looking for work; if you are interesting in hiring me for a job in data science or another field that you feel I would be suited for, please contact me at dylan@dylancromer.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
